Chance Murphy

734 South Division St. Ann Arbor MI, 48104 231-313-1883 chancem@umich.edu www.chancemurphy.com

About:

I am an experienced graphic designer residing in Ann Arbor, MI. During my schooling and work experience as a graphic designer, I have developed a keen eye for what goes together, as well as gained valuable experience working with clients and team members. I have also developed a strong interest in UI/UX design during this time due to my interest in the design of user interfaces for software systems.

Design:

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Indesign
- Adobe Illustrator
- Sketch
- Adobe Xd
- InVision
- Protoshare
- Wordpress

Programming:

- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

Education:

Master of Science in Information University of Michigan School of Information Ann Arbor, MI April 2020

Area of Study: Human Computer Interaction/ User Experience & Design

Bachelor of Arts Siena Heights University Adrian, MI May 2018

Major: Computers and Information Systems

Minor: Graphic Design

Experience:

Junior Graphic Desinger Artonic Web, Tecumseh, MI Intern, July 2017-April 2018 Junior Designer, April 2018 - Present

- Created wireframes for websites and software programs.
- Designd digital graphics, ads and banners.
- Organized and simplified website navigation for clients.
- Custom HTML, CSS, and Javascript coding.
- Designed various forms of print and digital media (Logos, Sales Sheets, infographics, etc.)

Freelance Developer May 2015-Present

- Designed and developed websites using Wordpress and HTML.
- Implemented e-commerce systems for clients.
- Created logos and other branding materials for clients.
- Created various forms of print media for clients. (Sales sheets, banners, flyers, bussiness cards, newletters, etc.)